 {
	"title": "Back To The Future",
	"questions":
		[{"question": "What is the name of the farmer who breeds pine trees?",
		"choices": ["Red Thomas", "Peabody", "Goldie Wilson", "George"],
		"answer": "Peabody"},
		
		{"question": "What year does Marty, Doc and Jennifer travel into the future?",
		"choices": [1955, 2015, 2020, 2018],
		"answer": 2015},

		{"question": "Why was Marty's fax from Fujitosan erased?",
		"choices": ["His future hasn't been written yet","Needles got pinned with the scam","Marty stole the Sports Almanac","The Time Machine was destroyed"],
		"answer": "His future hasn't been written yet"},

		{"question": "What football team wins when Biff gets the Almanac in 1955",
		"choices": ["Stanford","UCLA","Ohio State","Penn State"],
		"answer": "UCLA"},

		{"question": "What is the name of the HoverBoard Griff owns?",
		"choices": ["El Torro","Mad-Dog","Hornet","Pit-Bull"],
		"answer": "Pit-Bull"},

		{"question": "What level does Loranne hydrate her Pizza",
		"choices": ["Level 2","Level 3","Level 4","Level 5"],
		"answer": "Level 4"},

		{"question": "Who's number does Jennifer give Marty in the beginning of the 1st movie?",
		"choices": ["Her mom's","Her's","Her work number","Her grandmother's"],
		"answer": "Her grandmother's"},

		{"question": "What Key is \"Johnny B. Goode\" in?",
		"choices": ["C","B","D","E"],
		"answer": "B"},

		{"question": "What figure is at the top of Biff's cane?",
		"choices": ["A Skull","A Pit-Bull","A Dollar Sign","A Fist"],
		"answer": "A Fist"},

		{"question": "How does Biff pay for his taxi",
		"choices": ["Bitcoin","His fingerprint","He doesn't pay","He puts it on his tab"],
		"answer": "His fingerprint"},

		{"question": "Where is all the best stuff made?",
		"choices": ["Japan","Korea","China","The Moon"],
		"answer": "Japan"},

		{"question": "What object signals the 'Point of no return'?",
		"choices": ["Water Tower","Windmill","Barn","The Dead End Sign"],
		"answer": "Windmill"}]
}